export const aiQuizData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "AI aims to make machines capable of:",
    choices: ["Printing", "Human-like intelligence", "Sleeping", "Storing files"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which field trains models using data?",
    choices: ["Accounting", "Robotics", "Machine Learning", "Animation"],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Siri and Google Assistant are examples of:",
    choices: ["Voice-controlled AI", "Databases", "Malware", "Operating systems"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "The brain of an AI model is called:",
    choices: ["Server", "Neural Network", "Protocol", "Dataset"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Computer vision focuses on:",
    choices: ["Data compression", "Audio editing", "Image and video understanding", "Hardware repair"],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "AI uses large data to:",
    choices: ["Delete files", "Improve predictions", "Reduce memory", "Slow systems"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Chatbots are used mainly for:",
    choices: ["Customer support", "Gaming", "Electricity", "Antivirus"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Training AI models requires:",
    choices: ["Disk defragmentation", "High computing power", "No data", "Low processing"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "The ethical concern in AI is:",
    choices: ["Job displacement", "Changing fonts", "Free Wi-Fi", "Dark mode"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "The ability of AI to improve on its own is called:",
    choices: ["Booting", "Formatting", "Learning", "Hacking"],
    correct: 2
  }
];